Franklin-Bache Papers 1707-1799 Mss.B.F85.ba
American Philosophical Society
- Franklin-Bache Papers, 1707-1799; B F85.ba; 4 lin. feet
  - Memo. of accounts. #2, n.d; Franklin, Benjamin
  - Memo. of accounts. #3, n.d; Franklin, Benjamin
  - Memorandum of accounts, #1, Franklin, William Temple
  - Memo. of accounts, #2, n.d; Franklin, William Temple
  - German money valuations, n.d
  - to Benjamin Franklin, n.d. (Monday); Grand, Ferdinand
  - to Comte de Maillebois, n.d. (Feb. 15); Jancourt, Marquis de
  - n.d. (Monday), Knox, Henry
  - n.d. (March 22), Lawrence, Mrs. and Mrs. Allen.
  - n.d. (Thursday morning), Le Roy, Jean Baptiste
  - Receipt for a book, n.d; Library Company of Philadelphia.
  - List of initials and sums of money
  - to Messrs. Franklin and Adams, n.d. (Thursday evening); Lloyd, Mr. and Mrs.
  - Priced list of printing supplies offered to Dr. Franklin, n.d; Luce and Fagnion
  - n.d, Maillebois, Yves Marie Demaretz, comte de
  - Bill for Benjamin Franklin Bache's schooling, April 20-Sept. 5, n.d; Marignac, Gabriel L.
  - Memo. concerning the Chaumont account, n.d
  - Memo. of accounts, n.d
  - Memo. re. M. Pieroux, n.d
  - to Benjamin Franklin, n.d; Mesmer, Franz Anton, 1734-1815
  - Machine for dressing flour, n.d; Milne, John.
  - Machine for dressing oat-meal, n.d; Milne, John.
  - Memo, n.d; Morel, Messrs. Veuve Dominique and fils.
  - n.d, Morellet, abbé
  - -- Founts cast, n.d; Passy press.
  - List of types. #1, n.d; Passy press.
  - List of types. #2, n.d; Passy press.
  - List of types in Benjamin Franklin's hand. #1, Passy press.
  - List of types in Benjamin Franklin's hand. #2, Passy press.
  - to Benjamin Franklin, n.d; Petrie, S.
  - n.d, Sabran, comtesse de
  - n.d. (Saturday, June 20), Sargent, John
  - n.d, Séqueville, François Pierre de
  - Prospectus for school, n.d; Sicard, [Louis?]
  - Les Commandemens de l'honnete homme, Teutry (Oversize X)
  - "Liberty", n.d; Watts, Isaac.
  - Fragment [contains names and amounts of money]
  - Passport, n.d; Printed by Benjamin Franklin (Oversize 1)
  - Queries proposed for discussion in conversation by Benjamin Franklin, n.d
  - Wrapper for material pertaining to financial matters, n.d
  - Benjamin Franklin's sketch of his garden at Passy, March 27, 1782., 1782 March 27; 1.0 Item(s); Sketch of garden.